Kenny Quach

Fullstack Developer

Innovative team player with a passion for continuous learning and over two years experience in development. Coming with sound knowledge of the app life cycles and the ability to implement backend technologies with frontend user interfaces. Recently back to job seeking status in hopes of finding a role that will also allow me to incorporate newly acquired Java tech stack knowledge

EXPERIENCE

Advanced Technology Solutions, Manalapan, NJ — Fullstack Developer

Oct 2019 - Apr 2020

- Integrated Autotask ticketing system with several SAP technologies including Concur to track expense items and costs
- Implemented OAuth 2.0 to ensure secure access of system and database
- Utilized Java to run Kinetic task jar to perform tasks on the backend
- Added React features such as hooks and higher order components for efficiency
- Communicated with project manager daily to discuss potential issues and progress
- Utilized various React libraries to to incorporate modern features in applications
- Mapped and designed database to store incoming user information
- Implemented testing of api's throughout several integrated applications

Crane AI, New York, NY — React Developer May 2018 - Jul 2019

- Created user interfaces and various components using ReactJS and React Native
- Involved in testing process to find bugs and other issues before products went into production
- Implemented backend technology such as MongoDB, NodeJS, and API's to receive and store data from client side applications
- Worked with Coinbase's digital currency API for several cryptocurrency clients
- Took part in daily SCRUM meetings to discuss project goals and requirements
- Performed unit testing in apps using Jest
- Involved in testing iOS application to ensure user experience is smooth and bug free
- Added redux across several applications for efficient state management

Contact

Phone: (917) 257-0115

Email: kquach229@gmail.com

Medium: https://kquach229.medium.com/ Github: https://github.com/kquach229

Site: https://kquach229.github.io/portfolio site v1/

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Typescript, Sass, MongoDB, express, NodeJS, ReactJS, React Native, Jest, PassportJs, Redux, Git, EJS, Bootstrap, Material UI, Java, Spring/Spring boot, Spring Security, Postgresql,

Tools

Postman, MongDB Compass, Github Desktop, Netlify

Certifications

Google Analytics Certification

EDUCATION

Rutgers University, Newark, NJ — B.S in Supply Chain Management

Aug 2012 - May 2017